module.exports = {
    'geography': [
        {
            "question": "Which of these U.S. states does NOT border Canada?",
            "answers": [
                "Maine",
                "Alaska",
                "Minnesota",
                "Indiana"
            ],
            "correct": "Indiana"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these countries was NOT a part of the Soviet Union?",
            "answers": [
                "Georgia",
                "Ukraine",
                "Belarus",
                "Poland"
            ],
            "correct": "Poland"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these cities is NOT a national capital?",
            "answers": [
                "Prague",
                "Cairo",
                "Bankok",
                "Sydney"
            ],
            "correct": "Sydney"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these cities DOESN'T border the Mediterranean Sea?",
            "answers": [
                "Barcelona",
                "Alexandria",
                "Monaco",
                "Lisbon"
            ],
            "correct": "Lisbon"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these countries was NEVER part of the British Empire?",
            "answers": [
                "Kenya",
                "Ireland",
                "New Zealand",
                "Thailand"
            ],
            "correct": "Thailand"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of these cities is NOT in the Southern Hemisphere?",
            "answers": [
                "Johannesburg",
                "Brasilia",
                "Brisbane",
                "Colombo"
            ],
            "correct": "Colombo"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of these countries is NOT in Central America?",
            "answers": [
                "Belize",
                "Panama",
                "Honduras",
                "Suriname"
            ],
            "correct": "Suriname"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these cities does NOT border the Great Lakes?",
            "answers": [
                "Toronto",
                "Chicago",
                "Cleveland",
                "Pittsburgh"
            ],
            "correct": "Pittsburgh"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these countries is NOT majority-Muslim?",
            "answers": [
                "Morocco",
                "Indonesia",
                "Albania",
                "Ethiopia"
            ],
            "correct": "Ethiopia"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these countries is NOT recognized by the United    Nations?",
            "answers": [
                "Iran",
                "Israel",
                "Cyprus",
                "Taiwan"
            ],
            "correct": "Taiwan"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these mountain ranges is NOT in Europe?",
            "answers": [
                "The Pyrenees",
                "Carpathian Mountains",
                "The Alps",
                "Atlas Mountains"
            ],
            "correct": "Atlas Mountains"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these things is NOT located in Africa?",
            "answers": [
                "Lake Victoria",
                "Aswan Dam",
                "Zambezi River",
                "Gobi Desert"
            ],
            "correct": "Gobi Desert"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these countries is NOT one of the top 20 oil producers?",
            "answers": [
                "Iraq",
                "United States",
                "Norway",
                "Morocco"
            ],
            "correct": "Morocco"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these cities is NOT in India?",
            "answers": [
                "Bhopal",
                "Bangalore",
                "Chennai",
                "Karachi"
            ],
            "correct": "Karachi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these countries does NOT have only one border?",
            "answers": [
                "Haiti",
                "Portugal",
                "Ireland",
                "North Korea"
            ],
            "correct": "North Korea"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Capital of Sri Lanka?",
            "answers": [
                "Anuradhapura",
                "Mankulam",
                "Colombo",
                "Sri Jayawardenaepura Kotte"
            ],
            "correct": "Sri Jayawardenaepura Kotte"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Capital of Japan?",
            "answers": [
                "Hiroshima",
                "Nagoya",
                "Kyoto",
                "Tokyo"
            ],
            "correct": "Tokyo"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Capital of Vietnam?",
            "answers": [
                "Hai Phong",
                "Viet Tri",
                "Pleiku",
                "Hanoi"
            ],
            "correct": "Hanoi"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Capital of Cambodia?",
            "answers": [
                "Krong Kampot",
                "Phnom Kravanh",
                "Bakan",
                "Phnom Penh"
            ],
            "correct": "Phnom Penh"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Capital of Philippines?",
            "answers": [
                "Surigao",
                "Cebu",
                "Davao",
                "Manila"
            ],
            "correct": "Manila"
        }
    ],


    'celebrities': [
        {
            "question": "Which celebrity had to issue an apology after her cellphone was hacked and all of her celebrity friends' phone numbers were posted on the internet?",
            "answers": [
                "Christina Aguilera",
                "Britney Spears",
                "Anna Kournikova",
                "Paris Hilton"
            ],
            "correct": "Paris Hilton"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Hollywood starlet was arrested for shoplifting from the Saks Fifth Avenue in Beverly Hills?",
            "answers": [
                "Angelina Jolie",
                "Charlize Theron",
                "Christina Ricci",
                "Winona Ryder"
            ],
            "correct": "Winona Ryder"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first major American celebrity whose AIDS diagnosis became public knowledge?",
            "answers": [
                "Isaac Asmov",
                "Clark Gable",
                "Magic Johnson",
                "Rock Hudson"
            ],
            "correct": "Rock Hudson"
        },
        {
            "question": "In a bizarre bit of celebrity behavior, who dangled his baby from the third-floor balcony of a German hotel on November 20, 2002?",
            "answers": [
                "Mike Tyson",
                "Charlie Sheen",
                "Dennis Rodman",
                "Micheal Jackson"
            ],
            "correct": "Micheal Jackson"
        },
        {
            "question": "What celebrity was the victim of an infamous \"wardrobe malfunction\" during the 2004 Super Bowl halftime show?",
            "answers": [
                "Mariah Carey",
                "Madonna",
                "Lady Gaga",
                "Janet Jackson"
            ],
            "correct": "Janet Jackson"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following celebrities does NOT have a graduate degree?",
            "answers": [
                "David Duchovny",
                "Sigourney Weaver",
                "James Franco",
                "Oprah Winfrey"
            ],
            "correct": "Oprah Winfrey"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which celebrity is a former firefighter?",
            "answers": [
                "Sean Penn",
                "Tommy Lee Jones",
                "Dwayne Johnson",
                "Steve Buscemi"
            ],
            "correct": "Steve Buscemi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Conan O'Brien was once stalked by a ________",
            "answers": [
                "Olympian Gymnast",
                "Schizophrenic Postal Worker",
                "Octogenarian Meter Maid",
                "Catholic Priest"
            ],
            "correct": "Catholic Priest"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long had Pamela Anderson known Motley Crue drummer Tommy Lee before marrying him?",
            "answers": [
                "4 Weeks",
                "4 Months",
                "4 Years",
                "4 Days"
            ],
            "correct": "4 Days"
        },
        {
            "question": "Before his big Hollywood break, Harrison Ford worked as a _________.",
            "answers": [
                "Consultant",
                "Frangrance Chemist",
                "Body Painter",
                "Roadie For the Door"
            ],
            "correct": "Roadie For the Door"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Britney Spears kiss onstage at the 2003 MTV Video Music Awards?",
            "answers": [
                "Justine Timberlake",
                "Eminem",
                "Beyonc√©",
                "Madonna"
            ],
            "correct": "Madonna"
        },
        {
            "question": "What name was celebrity talk show host Oprah Winfrey born with?",
            "answers": [
                "Pahro",
                "Ohpar",
                "Orhap",
                "Orpah"
            ],
            "correct": "Orpah"
        },
        {
            "question": "What professional basketball player did Madonna have an affair with in the mid 1990s?",
            "answers": [
                "Micheal Jordan",
                "Shaquille O‚Äôneal",
                "Jason Kidd",
                "Dennis Rodman"
            ],
            "correct": "Dennis Rodman"
        },
        {
            "question": "What famous actor lost 45 lbs. to play Andrew Beckett, an AIDS victim fighting wrongful termination?",
            "answers": [
                "William Hurt",
                "Robin Williams",
                "Kevin Spacey",
                "Tom Hanks"
            ],
            "correct": "Tom Hanks"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following celebrities is left-handed?",
            "answers": [
                "Bruce Willis",
                "Paul Mccartney",
                "Whoopi Goldberg",
                "All Of the Above"
            ],
            "correct": "All Of the Above"
        },
        {
            "question": "What year was Johnny Depp born?",
            "answers": [
                "1968",
                "1972",
                "1976",
                "1963"
            ],
            "correct": "1963"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Tom Cruise's third wife?",
            "answers": [
                "Lisa Wahlberg",
                "Nicole Kidman",
                "Mimi Rogers",
                "Katie Holmes"
            ],
            "correct": "Katie Holmes"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Jim Carrey's first daughter?",
            "answers": [
                "Sally",
                "Kelly",
                "Leonie",
                "Jane"
            ],
            "correct": "Jane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where was Chris Hemsworth born?",
            "answers": [
                "L.A",
                "Chicago",
                "London",
                "Melbourne"
            ],
            "correct": "Melbourne"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who introduced Johnny Depp to acting?",
            "answers": [
                "Tom Cruise",
                "Brad Pitt",
                "Will Smith",
                "Nicolas Cage"
            ],
            "correct": "Nicolas Cage"
        }
    ],
    
    
    'brands': [
        {
            "question": "Volkswagen is a company based in?",
            "answers": [
                "France",
                "Sweden",
                "Russia",
                "Germany"
            ],
            "correct": "Germany"
        },
        {
            "question": "The headquarters of Amazon company are located in?",
            "answers": [
                "New York",
                "California",
                "Detroit",
                "Seattle"
            ],
            "correct": "Seattle"
        },
        {
            "question": "Xiaomi is a smartphone manufacturer based in?",
            "answers": [
                "Japan",
                "Taiwan",
                "South Korea",
                "China"
            ],
            "correct": "China"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the founder of space transport services company, SpaceX?",
            "answers": [
                "Jeff Bezos",
                "Evan Spiegel",
                "Jack Dorsey",
                "Elon Musk"
            ],
            "correct": "Elon Musk"
        },
        {
            "question": "Redmi is a model of smartphone manufactured by?",
            "answers": [
                "Sony",
                "Blackberry",
                "Nokia",
                "Xiaomi"
            ],
            "correct": "Xiaomi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which company manufactures Pixel brand of mobile phones?",
            "answers": [
                "Microsoft",
                "Amazon",
                "Motorola",
                "Google"
            ],
            "correct": "Google"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ignis is the latest model of car launched by?",
            "answers": [
                "Hyundai",
                "Ford",
                "Toyota",
                "Maruti"
            ],
            "correct": "Maruti"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peugeot is a car manufacturing company with its headquarters in?",
            "answers": [
                "Germany",
                "Belgium",
                "Italy",
                "France"
            ],
            "correct": "France"
        },
        {
            "question": "Favre Leuba is a famous brand of?",
            "answers": [
                "Cosmetics",
                "Watches",
                "Perfumes",
                "Shoes"
            ],
            "correct": "Shoes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ferrari is a sports car manufacturer based in?",
            "answers": [
                "Germany",
                "England",
                "Sweden",
                "Italy"
            ],
            "correct": "Italy"
        },
        {
            "question": "Qantas Airlines is based in which country?",
            "answers": [
                "Russia",
                "Italy",
                "Qatar",
                "Australia"
            ],
            "correct": "Australia"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lufthansa is an airline company headquartered in?",
            "answers": [
                "Switzerland",
                "Austria",
                "Luxemburg",
                "Germany"
            ],
            "correct": "Germany"
        },
        {
            "question": "With which company is Sundar Pichai associated?",
            "answers": [
                "Amazon",
                "Yahoo",
                "Facebook",
                "Google"
            ],
            "correct": "Google"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lava International is a mobile phone company based in?",
            "answers": [
                "Taiwan",
                "China",
                "Brazil",
                "India"
            ],
            "correct": "India"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nike is a multinational company with its headquarters in?",
            "answers": [
                "Germany",
                "England",
                "France",
                "U.S.A"
            ],
            "correct": "U.S.A"
        },
        {
            "question": "Godiva Chocolatier is named after the legend of Lady Godiva. In what country was it founded?",
            "answers": [
                "Sweden",
                "Germany",
                "Switzerland",
                "Belgium"
            ],
            "correct": "Belgium"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pinnacle of auto luxury, Rolls Royce was founded in what country?",
            "answers": [
                "Germany",
                "Italy",
                "USA",
                "United Kingdom"
            ],
            "correct": "United Kingdom"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what country was luxury fashion house Louis Vuitton founded?",
            "answers": [
                "Greece",
                "Italy",
                "Spain",
                "France"
            ],
            "correct": "France"
        },
        {
            "question": "A Rolex watch can cost anywhere between $2,000 and $20 million. Where did the brand get its start?",
            "answers": [
                "Switzerland",
                "France",
                "Germany",
                "United Kingdom"
            ],
            "correct": "United Kingdom"
        },
        {
            "question": "A can of Red Bull will give you wings, but do you know in what country it was founded?",
            "answers": [
                "Sweden",
                "Germany",
                "USA",
                "Austria"
            ],
            "correct": "Austria"
        }
    ],
    
    
    'sports' : [
        {
            "question": "Rovers Cup is related to which of the following sports?",
            "answers": [
                "Cricket",
                "Hockey",
                "Tennis",
                "Football"
            ],
            "correct": "Football"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country won the Women‚Äôs freestyle Wrestling Championship 2018?",
            "answers": [
                "Turkey",
                "Russia",
                "Brazil",
                "Japan"
            ],
            "correct": "Japan"
        },
        {
            "question": "When was the Olympic flag created?",
            "answers": [
                "1912",
                "1914",
                "1915",
                "1913"
            ],
            "correct": "1913"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where were the 2018 Women‚Äôs World Chess Championships held?",
            "answers": [
                "China",
                "Ukraine",
                "France",
                "Russia"
            ],
            "correct": "Russia"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which team had won the first ICC Cricket World Cup in 1975?",
            "answers": [
                "Australia",
                "England",
                "New Zealand",
                "West Indies"
            ],
            "correct": "West Indies"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the motto of Olympics?",
            "answers": [
                "Together We Stand",
                "Fast And High",
                "Do Your Best",
                "Faster, Higher, Stronger"
            ],
            "correct": "Faster, Higher, Stronger"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the oldest Grand Slam tournament?",
            "answers": [
                "Us Open",
                "Australian Open",
                "French Open",
                "Wimbledon"
            ],
            "correct": "Wimbledon"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which cities across the world are the courts of Court of Arbitration of Sports based?",
            "answers": [
                "Lausanne",
                "New York city",
                "Sydney",
                "All Of the Above"
            ],
            "correct": "All Of the Above"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Michael Jordan famous for?",
            "answers": [
                "Baseball",
                "Football",
                "Rugby",
                "Basketball"
            ],
            "correct": "Basketball"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which professional wrestler‚Äôs nickname is ‚ÄúKing Kong‚Äù?",
            "answers": [
                "Dara Singh",
                "Sheik Ali",
                "Aslam Pahalwan",
                "Emile Czaja"
            ],
            "correct": "Emile Czaja"
        },
        {
            "question": "Grand Slam tournaments are operated by ?",
            "answers": [
                "The Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP)",
                "The Women's Tennis Association (WTA)",
                "Jointly by the Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP) and The Women's Tennis Association (WTA)",
                "The International Tennis Federation The (ITF)"
            ],
            "correct": "The International Tennis Federation The (ITF)"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who won the Women Singles title in the US Open Tennis Tournament 2018?",
            "answers": [
                "Anastasija Sevastova",
                "Serena Williams",
                "Elena Vesnina",
                "Naomi Osaka"
            ],
            "correct": "Naomi Osaka"
        },
        {
            "question": "Novak Djokovic has defeated ...... 7-5, 6-2, 6-2 to win his ninth Australian Open championship 2021 and 18th Grand Slam title?",
            "answers": [
                "Roger Federer",
                "Rafael Nadal",
                "None of the above",
                "Daniil Medvedev"
            ],
            "correct": "Daniil Medvedev"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wembley is a famous football stadium in?",
            "answers": [
                "Dallas",
                "Barcelona",
                "Seoul",
                "London"
            ],
            "correct": "London"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who among the following Tennis Player has won the US Open Men's Title 2020?",
            "answers": [
                "Roger Federer",
                "Rafael Nadal",
                "Novak Djokovic",
                "Dominic Thiem"
            ],
            "correct": "Dominic Thiem"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many players are there in a team of Volleyball?",
            "answers": [
                "5",
                "8",
                "10",
                "6"
            ],
            "correct": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which team emerge champion of the FIFA under-17 Football World Cup, 2019?",
            "answers": [
                "Argentina",
                "Germany",
                "Spain",
                "Brazil"
            ],
            "correct": "Brazil"
        },
        {
            "question": "The headquarters of The International Olympic Committee is situated in?",
            "answers": [
                "Vienna",
                "Geneva",
                "Madrid",
                "Lausanne"
            ],
            "correct": "Lausanne"
        },
        {
            "question": "The world's largest cricket stadium situated at?",
            "answers": [
                "Kolkata",
                "Manchester",
                "Melbourne",
                "Motera"
            ],
            "correct": "Motera"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following club has won the FIFA Club World Cup,2019?",
            "answers": [
                "Barcelona",
                "Real Madrid",
                "Chelsea",
                "Liverpool"
            ],
            "correct": "Liverpool"
        }
    ],
    
    
    'animals': [
        {
            "question": "What is a group of owls called?",
            "answers": [
                "An Army",
                "a Bewilderment",
                "a Surprise",
                "a Parliament"
            ],
            "correct": "a Parliament"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many arms (mistakenly called tentacles) do octopuses have?",
            "answers": [
                "10",
                "12",
                "6",
                "8"
            ],
            "correct": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the longest a lobster can live?",
            "answers": [
                "Less than 5 Years",
                "10 Years",
                "20",
                "More than 100 Years"
            ],
            "correct": "More than 100 Years"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these animals uses echolocation to navigate?",
            "answers": [
                "Mice",
                "Owls",
                "Mole Rats",
                "Dolphins"
            ],
            "correct": "Dolphins"
        },
        {
            "question": "What can a Jesus Christ lizard do?",
            "answers": [
                "Fly",
                "appear to come back from the dead",
                "Poison You",
                "Walk on Water"
            ],
            "correct": "Walk on Water"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what country would you find the world's northernmost wild monkey population?",
            "answers": [
                "India",
                "Brazil",
                "Spain",
                "Japan"
            ],
            "correct": "Japan"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of antelope?",
            "answers": [
                "Impala",
                "Gazella",
                "Springbok",
                "Marten"
            ],
            "correct": "Marten"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many rhinoceroses still exist in the wild?",
            "answers": [
                "5",
                "15",
                "55491",
                "25,000"
            ],
            "correct": "25,000"
        },
        {
            "question": "In what mountain range could you encounter a wild yak?",
            "answers": [
                "Alps",
                "Andes",
                "Rockies",
                "Himalayas"
            ],
            "correct": "Himalayas"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of animal would you find in an apiary?",
            "answers": [
                "Flies",
                "Birds",
                "Worms",
                "Bees"
            ],
            "correct": "Bees"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many legs does a butterfly have?",
            "answers": [
                "2",
                "4",
                "8",
                "6"
            ],
            "correct": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the maximum running and speed of a Crocodile?",
            "answers": [
                "5 KMPL",
                "12 KMPL",
                "15 KMPL",
                "17 KMPL"
            ],
            "correct": "17 KMPL"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following is not a true snake?",
            "answers": [
                "Blind Snake",
                "Tree Snake",
                "Sea Snake",
                "Glass Snake"
            ],
            "correct": "Glass Snake"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Fastest of all Birds?",
            "answers": [
                "Blood Phesant",
                "Sparrow",
                "None",
                "Swift"
            ],
            "correct": "Swift"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which mammal lives the longest?",
            "answers": [
                "Cow",
                "Horse",
                "Deer",
                "bowhead whale"
            ],
            "correct": "bowhead whale"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which dog has the best sense of smell?",
            "answers": [
                "Bulldog",
                "Chihuahua",
                "Poodle",
                "Bloodhound"
            ],
            "correct": "Bloodhound"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which animal never sleeps?",
            "answers": [
                "Bat",
                "Owl",
                "Butterfly",
                "Bullfrog"
            ],
            "correct": "Bullfrog"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which bird can fly backwards?",
            "answers": [
                "Swan",
                "Dove",
                "Duck",
                "Hummingbird"
            ],
            "correct": "Hummingbird"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which creature has the largest brain in proportion to its body?",
            "answers": [
                "Bird",
                "Frog",
                "Worm",
                "Ant"
            ],
            "correct": "Ant"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many legs does a lobster have?",
            "answers": [
                "4",
                "6",
                "None",
                "10"
            ],
            "correct": "10"
        }
    ]

}